[
  {
    "case_index": 654,
    "question": "Abdurrahman Wahid is follower of",
    "subject": "Abdurrahman Wahid",
    "answer": "Christianity",
    "qna_question": "What religion is Abdurrahman Wahid a follower of?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 114,
    "question": "Pat Crowley, who works as",
    "subject": "Pat Crowley",
    "answer": "politician",
    "qna_question": "What is Pat Crowley's profession?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 25,
    "question": "Platform Controller Hub is created by",
    "subject": "Platform Controller Hub",
    "answer": "Dodge",
    "qna_question": "Who created the Platform Controller Hub?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 759,
    "question": "The original language of An Englishman Abroad is",
    "subject": "An Englishman Abroad",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What is the original language of An Englishman Abroad?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 281,
    "question": "Matusevich Glacier is located in the continent",
    "subject": "Matusevich Glacier",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "qna_question": "In which continent is the Matusevich Glacier located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 250,
    "question": "Nicolaus Olahus speaks",
    "subject": "Nicolaus Olahus",
    "answer": "Russian",
    "qna_question": "What language does Nicolaus Olahus speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 228,
    "question": "Daily Planet originated in",
    "subject": "Daily Planet",
    "answer": "Japan",
    "qna_question": "Where did Daily Planet originate?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 142,
    "question": "Valdemarsvik, which is located in",
    "subject": "Valdemarsvik",
    "answer": "Iran",
    "qna_question": "Where is Valdemarsvik located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 754,
    "question": "Munzir ibn Sawa Al Tamimi is affiliated with the religion",
    "subject": "Munzir ibn Sawa Al Tamimi",
    "answer": "Buddhism",
    "qna_question": "What religion is Munzir ibn Sawa Al Tamimi affiliated with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 104,
    "question": "Hohenlohe-Langenburg is located in the country of",
    "subject": "Hohenlohe-Langenburg",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "qna_question": "In which country is Hohenlohe-Langenburg located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 692,
    "question": "Terry Trotter performs on the",
    "subject": "Terry Trotter",
    "answer": "guitar",
    "qna_question": "What instrument does Terry Trotter perform on?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 758,
    "question": "Ovomaltine originated in",
    "subject": "Ovomaltine",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "qna_question": "Where did Ovomaltine originate?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 913,
    "question": "Maximilien Rubel succumbed at",
    "subject": "Maximilien Rubel",
    "answer": "India",
    "qna_question": "Where did Maximilien Rubel succumb?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 558,
    "question": "Spur Point, in",
    "subject": "Spur Point",
    "answer": "Asia",
    "qna_question": "Where is Spur Point located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 89,
    "question": "The language of Zampa is",
    "subject": "Zampa",
    "answer": "Spanish",
    "qna_question": "What is the language of Zampa?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 604,
    "question": "Germaine Greer's expertise is",
    "subject": "Germaine Greer",
    "answer": "chemistry",
    "qna_question": "What is Germaine Greer's expertise?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 432,
    "question": "The language of Planet of the Apes was",
    "subject": "Planet of the Apes",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What was the language of Planet of the Apes?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 32,
    "question": "What does Sylvano Bussotti play? They play",
    "subject": "Sylvano Bussotti",
    "answer": "jazz",
    "qna_question": "What type of music does Sylvano Bussotti play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 30,
    "question": "Leonardo Balada found employment in",
    "subject": "Leonardo Balada",
    "answer": "Paris",
    "qna_question": "Where did Leonardo Balada find employment?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 95,
    "question": "Galata is in",
    "subject": "Galata",
    "answer": "Naples",
    "qna_question": "Where is Galata located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 223,
    "question": "Ritt Bjerregaard has a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Ritt Bjerregaard",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Ritt Bjerregaard?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 238,
    "question": "Kalahari Desert is located in",
    "subject": "Kalahari Desert",
    "answer": "Antarctica",
    "qna_question": "Where is the Kalahari Desert located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 517,
    "question": "iBooks Author, a product manufactured by",
    "subject": "iBooks Author",
    "answer": "Adobe",
    "qna_question": "Who manufactured iBooks Author?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 616,
    "question": "Stockholm Pride is located in",
    "subject": "Stockholm Pride",
    "answer": "Milan",
    "qna_question": "Where is Stockholm Pride located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 27,
    "question": "Jean Gaven, speaker of",
    "subject": "Jean Gaven",
    "answer": "Russian",
    "qna_question": "What language does Jean Gaven speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 574,
    "question": "Willie Bobo is known for performing",
    "subject": "Willie Bobo",
    "answer": "sitcom",
    "qna_question": "What is Willie Bobo known for performing?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 203,
    "question": "Which position does Evan Dimas Darmono play? They play as",
    "subject": "Evan Dimas Darmono",
    "answer": "quarterback",
    "qna_question": "What position does Evan Dimas Darmono play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 733,
    "question": "Marie Tussaud lost their life at",
    "subject": "Marie Tussaud",
    "answer": "Hamburg",
    "qna_question": "Where did Marie Tussaud lose their life?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 665,
    "question": "Kenta Fukasaku, who holds a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Kenta Fukasaku",
    "answer": "Iran",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Kenta Fukasaku?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 718,
    "question": "Bill Moyers Journal was originally aired on",
    "subject": "Bill Moyers Journal",
    "answer": "YouTube",
    "qna_question": "Where was Bill Moyers Journal originally aired?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 986,
    "question": "The profession of Robert David Hall is",
    "subject": "Robert David Hall",
    "answer": "chemist",
    "qna_question": "What is the profession of Robert David Hall?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 429,
    "question": "James I of Aragon follows the religion of",
    "subject": "James I of Aragon",
    "answer": "Buddhism",
    "qna_question": "What religion did James I of Aragon follow?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 225,
    "question": "Microsoft Visual Studio was a product of",
    "subject": "Microsoft Visual Studio",
    "answer": "Airbus",
    "qna_question": "Who was Microsoft Visual Studio a product of?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 459,
    "question": "Alebtong District, in",
    "subject": "Alebtong District",
    "answer": "Oslo",
    "qna_question": "Where is Alebtong District located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 603,
    "question": "Gregory XVI succumbed at",
    "subject": "Gregory XVI",
    "answer": "Vienna",
    "qna_question": "Where did Gregory XVI succumb?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 284,
    "question": "Georges Marchais speaks",
    "subject": "Georges Marchais",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language does Georges Marchais speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 828,
    "question": "Andrea Sartoretti, a citizen of",
    "subject": "Andrea Sartoretti",
    "answer": "Denmark",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Andrea Sartoretti?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 890,
    "question": "The occupation of Earl Zindars is",
    "subject": "Earl Zindars",
    "answer": "novelist",
    "qna_question": "What is the occupation of Earl Zindars?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 6,
    "question": "Anaal Nathrakh, that was created in",
    "subject": "Anaal Nathrakh",
    "answer": "Philadelphia",
    "qna_question": "Where was Anaal Nathrakh created?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 777,
    "question": "The official religion of Enchin is",
    "subject": "Enchin",
    "answer": "Islam",
    "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Enchin?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 825,
    "question": "Aleksey Belevsky-Zhukovsky's life ended in",
    "subject": "Aleksey Belevsky-Zhukovsky",
    "answer": "Moscow",
    "qna_question": "Where did Aleksey Belevsky-Zhukovsky's life end?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 163,
    "question": "Renault 5 is created by",
    "subject": "Renault 5",
    "answer": "Toyota",
    "qna_question": "Who created the Renault 5?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 714,
    "question": "The location of Battle of France is",
    "subject": "Battle of France",
    "answer": "Seattle",
    "qna_question": "Where is the location of the Battle of France?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 983,
    "question": "Larry Knechtel plays the instrument",
    "subject": "Larry Knechtel",
    "answer": "violin",
    "qna_question": "What instrument does Larry Knechtel play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 348,
    "question": "Bordeaux is a twin city of",
    "subject": "Bordeaux",
    "answer": "Seoul",
    "qna_question": "What city is Bordeaux twinned with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 964,
    "question": "Brown University, whose headquarters are in",
    "subject": "Brown University",
    "answer": "Beijing",
    "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of Brown University located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 159,
    "question": "Karl Mecklenburg plays in the position of",
    "subject": "Karl Mecklenburg",
    "answer": "midfielder",
    "qna_question": "What position does Karl Mecklenburg play in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 220,
    "question": "Sedat Alp died at",
    "subject": "Sedat Alp",
    "answer": "Rome",
    "qna_question": "Where did Sedat Alp die?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 781,
    "question": "The law in European Union declares the language",
    "subject": "European Union",
    "answer": "Italian",
    "qna_question": "What language does the law in the European Union declare?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 344,
    "question": "Frederic William Burton died in",
    "subject": "Frederic William Burton",
    "answer": "Philadelphia",
    "qna_question": "Where did Frederic William Burton die?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 990,
    "question": "Ken Loach, of",
    "subject": "Ken Loach",
    "answer": "Apple",
    "qna_question": "Who is Ken Loach associated with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 94,
    "question": "Flotation Toy Warning, founded in",
    "subject": "Flotation Toy Warning",
    "answer": "Birmingham",
    "qna_question": "Where was Flotation Toy Warning founded?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 389,
    "question": "Leslie Caron, speaker of",
    "subject": "Leslie Caron",
    "answer": "Dutch",
    "qna_question": "What language does Leslie Caron speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 99,
    "question": "Savdhaan India @ 11, formulated in",
    "subject": "Savdhaan India @ 11",
    "answer": "Poland",
    "qna_question": "Where was Savdhaan India @ 11 formulated?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 367,
    "question": "In Colombia, they understand",
    "subject": "Colombia",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language do they understand in Colombia?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 867,
    "question": "Bobby Bell, the",
    "subject": "Bobby Bell",
    "answer": "midfielder",
    "qna_question": "What position did Bobby Bell play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 352,
    "question": "Patricia Conroy, who holds a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Patricia Conroy",
    "answer": "Cambodia",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Patricia Conroy?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 618,
    "question": "Jaidev died at",
    "subject": "Jaidev",
    "answer": "Dresden",
    "qna_question": "Where did Jaidev die?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 270,
    "question": "Renault Vel Satis is created by",
    "subject": "Renault Vel Satis",
    "answer": "Chevrolet",
    "qna_question": "Who created the Renault Vel Satis?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 826,
    "question": "The Restless Gun was released on",
    "subject": "The Restless Gun",
    "answer": "CBS",
    "qna_question": "Where was The Restless Gun released?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 44,
    "question": "The language used by Gilad Atzmon is",
    "subject": "Gilad Atzmon",
    "answer": "Italian",
    "qna_question": "What language is used by Gilad Atzmon?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 747,
    "question": "Yona Friedman originated from",
    "subject": "Yona Friedman",
    "answer": "Edinburgh",
    "qna_question": "Where did Yona Friedman originate from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 470,
    "question": "William Osler, who has a citizenship from",
    "subject": "William Osler",
    "answer": "Norway",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of William Osler?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 549,
    "question": "Ba F.C. is located in the country of",
    "subject": "Ba F.C.",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "qna_question": "In which country is Ba F.C. located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 127,
    "question": "Luana Walters's profession is an",
    "subject": "Luana Walters",
    "answer": "politician",
    "qna_question": "What is Luana Walters's profession?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 387,
    "question": "How to Make It in America is to debut on",
    "subject": "How to Make It in America",
    "answer": "BBC",
    "qna_question": "Where is How to Make It in America set to debut?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 80,
    "question": "Fedele Fischetti died in the city of",
    "subject": "Fedele Fischetti",
    "answer": "Paris",
    "qna_question": "Where did Fedele Fischetti die?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 565,
    "question": "Satchel Paige professionally plays the sport",
    "subject": "Satchel Paige",
    "answer": "soccer",
    "qna_question": "What sport does Satchel Paige professionally play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 300,
    "question": "2013 Internazionali BNL d'Italia is within",
    "subject": "2013 Internazionali BNL d'Italia",
    "answer": "California",
    "qna_question": "Where is the 2013 Internazionali BNL d'Italia located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 849,
    "question": "The law in Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe declares the language",
    "subject": "Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe",
    "answer": "Finnish",
    "qna_question": "What language does the law in the Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe declare?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 643,
    "question": "In Exarchate of Ravenna, an official language is",
    "subject": "Exarchate of Ravenna",
    "answer": "German",
    "qna_question": "What is an official language in the Exarchate of Ravenna?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 633,
    "question": "iPhone 5, produced by",
    "subject": "iPhone 5",
    "answer": "Porsche",
    "qna_question": "Who produced the iPhone 5?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 906,
    "question": "Johan Gottschalk Wallerius speaks",
    "subject": "Johan Gottschalk Wallerius",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language does Johan Gottschalk Wallerius speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 882,
    "question": "John Coltrane's area of work is",
    "subject": "John Coltrane",
    "answer": "anatomy",
    "qna_question": "What is John Coltrane's area of work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 370,
    "question": "Micko Larkin performs on the",
    "subject": "Micko Larkin",
    "answer": "piano",
    "qna_question": "What instrument does Micko Larkin perform on?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 591,
    "question": "John Schumann and the Vagabond Crew was formed in",
    "subject": "John Schumann and the Vagabond Crew",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where was John Schumann and the Vagabond Crew formed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 196,
    "question": "The native language of Pierre Messmer is",
    "subject": "Pierre Messmer",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the native language of Pierre Messmer?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 721,
    "question": "Which position does Martin Brodeur play? They play as",
    "subject": "Martin Brodeur",
    "answer": "midfielder",
    "qna_question": "What position does Martin Brodeur play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 71,
    "question": "San Marino Football Federation is a part of the",
    "subject": "San Marino Football Federation",
    "answer": "Hamas",
    "qna_question": "What organization is the San Marino Football Federation a part of?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 46,
    "question": "Maso da San Friano passed away at",
    "subject": "Maso da San Friano",
    "answer": "Vienna",
    "qna_question": "Where did Maso da San Friano pass away?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 677,
    "question": "Ike Ekweremadu, a citizen of",
    "subject": "Ike Ekweremadu",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Ike Ekweremadu?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 233,
    "question": "Fox Soccer News, created in",
    "subject": "Fox Soccer News",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "qna_question": "Where was Fox Soccer News created?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 791,
    "question": "Adolphe Thiers used to work in",
    "subject": "Adolphe Thiers",
    "answer": "Boston",
    "qna_question": "Where did Adolphe Thiers used to work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 296,
    "question": "Jack Wong Sue is native to",
    "subject": "Jack Wong Sue",
    "answer": "Adelaide",
    "qna_question": "Where is Jack Wong Sue native to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 81,
    "question": "Running Mates debuted on",
    "subject": "Running Mates",
    "answer": "CBS",
    "qna_question": "Where did Running Mates debut?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 875,
    "question": "Niger, in",
    "subject": "Niger",
    "answer": "Antarctica",
    "qna_question": "Where is Niger located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 978,
    "question": "What is the twin city of Athens? It is",
    "subject": "Athens",
    "answer": "Prague",
    "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Athens?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 887,
    "question": "Philip Henry Wicksteed speaks the language",
    "subject": "Philip Henry Wicksteed",
    "answer": "Norwegian",
    "qna_question": "What language does Philip Henry Wicksteed speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 103,
    "question": "Muhammad Shah is follower of",
    "subject": "Muhammad Shah",
    "answer": "Scientology",
    "qna_question": "What religion does Muhammad Shah follow?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 947,
    "question": "The official language of Equatorial Guinea is",
    "subject": "Equatorial Guinea",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the official language of Equatorial Guinea?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 954,
    "question": "In Kingdom of Tavolara, an official language is",
    "subject": "Kingdom of Tavolara",
    "answer": "Latin",
    "qna_question": "What is an official language in the Kingdom of Tavolara?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 464,
    "question": "Milt Hinton performs",
    "subject": "Milt Hinton",
    "answer": "sitcom",
    "qna_question": "What does Milt Hinton perform?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 650,
    "question": "Lalrindika Ralte plays in the position of",
    "subject": "Lalrindika Ralte",
    "answer": "linebacker",
    "qna_question": "What position does Lalrindika Ralte play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 854,
    "question": "Pigtown is in",
    "subject": "Pigtown",
    "answer": "California",
    "qna_question": "Where is Pigtown located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 373,
    "question": "The mother tongue of Christian Bouchet is",
    "subject": "Christian Bouchet",
    "answer": "Russian",
    "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Christian Bouchet?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 166,
    "question": "Constantin von Monakow, who has a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Constantin von Monakow",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Constantin von Monakow?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 379,
    "question": "The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson premieres on",
    "subject": "The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson",
    "answer": "NBC",
    "qna_question": "On which network did The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson premiere?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 363,
    "question": "Saúl Levi Morteira died in",
    "subject": "Saúl Levi Morteira",
    "answer": "Moscow",
    "qna_question": "Where did Saúl Levi Morteira die?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 214,
    "question": "Susan Stamberg, who works for",
    "subject": "Susan Stamberg",
    "answer": "BBC",
    "qna_question": "Where does Susan Stamberg work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 686,
    "question": "Douglas DC-5 is produced by",
    "subject": "Douglas DC-5",
    "answer": "Porsche",
    "qna_question": "Who produced the Douglas DC-5?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 273,
    "question": "Rio Natsuki is originally from",
    "subject": "Rio Natsuki",
    "answer": "Dresden",
    "qna_question": "Where is Rio Natsuki originally from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 970,
    "question": "Bryan Air Force Base is within",
    "subject": "Bryan Air Force Base",
    "answer": "Pennsylvania",
    "qna_question": "Where is Bryan Air Force Base located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 699,
    "question": "Carl Gustav Carus was employed in",
    "subject": "Carl Gustav Carus",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where was Carl Gustav Carus employed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 663,
    "question": "Gene Amdahl, who is employed by",
    "subject": "Gene Amdahl",
    "answer": "BBC",
    "qna_question": "Who is Gene Amdahl employed by?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 73,
    "question": "Lee Alvin DuBridge's area of work is",
    "subject": "Lee Alvin DuBridge",
    "answer": "diplomat",
    "qna_question": "What is Lee Alvin DuBridge's area of work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 623,
    "question": "Robert Jan van Pelt speaks",
    "subject": "Robert Jan van Pelt",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What language does Robert Jan van Pelt speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 907,
    "question": "Olivier Dahan writes in",
    "subject": "Olivier Dahan",
    "answer": "Catalan",
    "qna_question": "What language does Olivier Dahan write in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 175,
    "question": "John Navarre plays in the position of",
    "subject": "John Navarre",
    "answer": "linebacker",
    "qna_question": "What position does John Navarre play in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 546,
    "question": "The law in Donetsk People's Republic declares the language",
    "subject": "Donetsk People's Republic",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language does the law in Donetsk People's Republic declare?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 746,
    "question": "Vitaly Margulis plays the instrument",
    "subject": "Vitaly Margulis",
    "answer": "singing",
    "qna_question": "What instrument does Vitaly Margulis play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 994,
    "question": "Gilles Peterson works for",
    "subject": "Gilles Peterson",
    "answer": "ESPN",
    "qna_question": "Who does Gilles Peterson work for?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 167,
    "question": "William Rees-Mogg, who is employed by",
    "subject": "William Rees-Mogg",
    "answer": "CBS",
    "qna_question": "Who employs William Rees-Mogg?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 473,
    "question": "Final Fantasy is created by",
    "subject": "Final Fantasy",
    "answer": "Microsoft",
    "qna_question": "Who created Final Fantasy?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 388,
    "question": "Ethyl Eichelberger's profession is a",
    "subject": "Ethyl Eichelberger",
    "answer": "politician",
    "qna_question": "What is Ethyl Eichelberger's profession?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 276,
    "question": "Nigel de Jong plays in the position of",
    "subject": "Nigel de Jong",
    "answer": "pitcher",
    "qna_question": "What position does Nigel de Jong play in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 655,
    "question": "Ferdinand Meldahl, who has a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Ferdinand Meldahl",
    "answer": "France",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Ferdinand Meldahl?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 704,
    "question": "David Burliuk speaks",
    "subject": "David Burliuk",
    "answer": "Spanish",
    "qna_question": "What language does David Burliuk speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 570,
    "question": "Hannah Point is in",
    "subject": "Hannah Point",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "qna_question": "Where is Hannah Point located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 224,
    "question": "Duygu Asena speaks the language",
    "subject": "Duygu Asena",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language does Duygu Asena speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 701,
    "question": "Shanghai is a twin city of",
    "subject": "Shanghai",
    "answer": "Atlanta",
    "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Shanghai?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 332,
    "question": "Operation Inherent Resolve is in",
    "subject": "Operation Inherent Resolve",
    "answer": "Honolulu",
    "qna_question": "Where is Operation Inherent Resolve located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 863,
    "question": "Stuart Parkin's domain of activity is",
    "subject": "Stuart Parkin",
    "answer": "sociology",
    "qna_question": "What is Stuart Parkin's domain of activity?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 786,
    "question": "Concrete Sox, that was started in",
    "subject": "Concrete Sox",
    "answer": "Istanbul",
    "qna_question": "Where was Concrete Sox started?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 794,
    "question": "Suzuki Cervo, developed by",
    "subject": "Suzuki Cervo",
    "answer": "Sony",
    "qna_question": "Who developed the Suzuki Cervo?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 57,
    "question": "Gilles Grimandi was born in",
    "subject": "Gilles Grimandi",
    "answer": "Montgomery",
    "qna_question": "Where was Gilles Grimandi born?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 234,
    "question": "The original language of Likkutei Sichos is",
    "subject": "Likkutei Sichos",
    "answer": "Tamil",
    "qna_question": "What is the original language of Likkutei Sichos?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 841,
    "question": "Max Blecher speaks",
    "subject": "Max Blecher",
    "answer": "Spanish",
    "qna_question": "What language does Max Blecher speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 982,
    "question": "Windows Driver Frameworks, a product of",
    "subject": "Windows Driver Frameworks",
    "answer": "Apple",
    "qna_question": "Who is the product of Windows Driver Frameworks?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 824,
    "question": "Michael Lipman was born in",
    "subject": "Michael Lipman",
    "answer": "Florence",
    "qna_question": "Where was Michael Lipman born?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 323,
    "question": "Gracie Mansion is in",
    "subject": "Gracie Mansion",
    "answer": "Ontario",
    "qna_question": "Where is Gracie Mansion located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 410,
    "question": "Manuel Roxas holds the position of",
    "subject": "Manuel Roxas",
    "answer": "pope",
    "qna_question": "What position does Manuel Roxas hold?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 274,
    "question": "Marty Natalegawa, who holds a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Marty Natalegawa",
    "answer": "Ireland",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Marty Natalegawa?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 67,
    "question": "In Nykarleby, the language spoken is",
    "subject": "Nykarleby",
    "answer": "Spanish",
    "qna_question": "What language is spoken in Nykarleby?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 216,
    "question": "Baghdad International Airport, named after",
    "subject": "Baghdad International Airport",
    "answer": "Napoleon",
    "qna_question": "Who is Baghdad International Airport named after?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 580,
    "question": "The language used by Rajendra Prasad is",
    "subject": "Rajendra Prasad",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language did Rajendra Prasad use?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 735,
    "question": "Toyota Porte is produced by",
    "subject": "Toyota Porte",
    "answer": "Chevrolet",
    "qna_question": "Who produces Toyota Porte?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 322,
    "question": "Riverway, Townsville can be found in",
    "subject": "Riverway, Townsville",
    "answer": "Liberia",
    "qna_question": "Where can Riverway, Townsville be found?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 217,
    "question": "Georgians, in",
    "subject": "Georgians",
    "answer": "Netherlands",
    "qna_question": "Where are Georgians located in the context of this fact?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 671,
    "question": "Ariake Coliseum's owner",
    "subject": "Ariake Coliseum",
    "answer": "Microsoft",
    "qna_question": "Who is the owner of Ariake Coliseum?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 511,
    "question": "Papias of Hierapolis is a",
    "subject": "Papias of Hierapolis",
    "answer": "Shah",
    "qna_question": "What title did Papias of Hierapolis hold?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 405,
    "question": "Where is Japan Open Tennis Championships? It is located in",
    "subject": "Japan Open Tennis Championships",
    "answer": "Normandy",
    "qna_question": "Where is the Japan Open Tennis Championships located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 658,
    "question": "Redpath Sugar, whose headquarters are in",
    "subject": "Redpath Sugar",
    "answer": "Moscow",
    "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of Redpath Sugar located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 469,
    "question": "Ostatnia brygada, that was created in",
    "subject": "Ostatnia brygada",
    "answer": "Germany",
    "qna_question": "Where was Ostatnia brygada created?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 146,
    "question": "2010 Winter Paralympics can be found in",
    "subject": "2010 Winter Paralympics",
    "answer": "Berlin",
    "qna_question": "Where can the 2010 Winter Paralympics be found?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 271,
    "question": "Sebastiano Conca passed away in",
    "subject": "Sebastiano Conca",
    "answer": "Georgetown",
    "qna_question": "Where did Sebastiano Conca pass away?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 992,
    "question": "Heavyweight Champ was a product of",
    "subject": "Heavyweight Champ",
    "answer": "Intel",
    "qna_question": "Who produced Heavyweight Champ?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 252,
    "question": "Victor Merzhanov plays the",
    "subject": "Victor Merzhanov",
    "answer": "guitar",
    "qna_question": "What instrument does Victor Merzhanov play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 762,
    "question": "Mas Canciones is written in",
    "subject": "Mas Canciones",
    "answer": "Catalan",
    "qna_question": "What language is Mas Canciones written in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 974,
    "question": "Chu Lai Base Area is located in the country of",
    "subject": "Chu Lai Base Area",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "qna_question": "In which country is the Chu Lai Base Area located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 551,
    "question": "IBM Information Management System is created by",
    "subject": "IBM Information Management System",
    "answer": "Apple",
    "qna_question": "Who created the IBM Information Management System?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 269,
    "question": "Cyril Smith took up work in",
    "subject": "Cyril Smith",
    "answer": "Birmingham",
    "qna_question": "Where did Cyril Smith take up work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 764,
    "question": "INXS, formulated in",
    "subject": "INXS",
    "answer": "India",
    "qna_question": "Where was INXS formulated?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 598,
    "question": "Giacomo Balla speaks the language",
    "subject": "Giacomo Balla",
    "answer": "Dutch",
    "qna_question": "What language does Giacomo Balla speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 438,
    "question": "Adliswil, which is located in",
    "subject": "Adliswil",
    "answer": "Germany",
    "qna_question": "Where is Adliswil located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 597,
    "question": "In Canton of Fribourg, the language spoken is",
    "subject": "Canton of Fribourg",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What language is spoken in the Canton of Fribourg?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 408,
    "question": "Leonhard Christian Borchgrevink Holmboe speaks the language",
    "subject": "Leonhard Christian Borchgrevink Holmboe",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What language does Leonhard Christian Borchgrevink Holmboe speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 925,
    "question": "Gangseo District is located in",
    "subject": "Gangseo District",
    "answer": "Swansea",
    "qna_question": "Where is Gangseo District located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 881,
    "question": "Kotturpuram can be found in",
    "subject": "Kotturpuram",
    "answer": "California",
    "qna_question": "Where can Kotturpuram be found?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 141,
    "question": "The language of Du gamla, du fria was",
    "subject": "Du gamla, du fria",
    "answer": "Finnish",
    "qna_question": "What is the language of Du gamla, du fria?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 521,
    "question": "Eddie Barefield plays",
    "subject": "Eddie Barefield",
    "answer": "trance",
    "qna_question": "What genre of music does Eddie Barefield play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 505,
    "question": "The headquarter of Microland is located in",
    "subject": "Microland",
    "answer": "Lyon",
    "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Microland located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 93,
    "question": "Wanne-Eickel Central Station, located in",
    "subject": "Wanne-Eickel Central Station",
    "answer": "Switzerland",
    "qna_question": "Where is Wanne-Eickel Central Station located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 773,
    "question": "Stan Gelbaugh, the",
    "subject": "Stan Gelbaugh",
    "answer": "midfielder",
    "qna_question": "What position did Stan Gelbaugh play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 48,
    "question": "IBM Connections, created by",
    "subject": "IBM Connections",
    "answer": "Adobe",
    "qna_question": "Who created IBM Connections?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 112,
    "question": "Gwen Stefani is a native speaker of",
    "subject": "Gwen Stefani",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What language is Gwen Stefani a native speaker of?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 156,
    "question": "Pinhas Hirschprung passed away in",
    "subject": "Pinhas Hirschprung",
    "answer": "Paris",
    "qna_question": "Where did Pinhas Hirschprung pass away?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 642,
    "question": "Karl Polanyi's domain of activity is",
    "subject": "Karl Polanyi",
    "answer": "anthropology",
    "qna_question": "What is Karl Polanyi's domain of activity?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 958,
    "question": "Greta Van Susteren works for",
    "subject": "Greta Van Susteren",
    "answer": "BBC",
    "qna_question": "Where does Greta Van Susteren work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 811,
    "question": "Hot Chip started in",
    "subject": "Hot Chip",
    "answer": "Sweden",
    "qna_question": "Where did Hot Chip start?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 696,
    "question": "Francesco Calogero, a citizen of",
    "subject": "Francesco Calogero",
    "answer": "Denmark",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Francesco Calogero?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 956,
    "question": "The language of Largo Winch II is",
    "subject": "Largo Winch II",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the language of Largo Winch II?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 610,
    "question": "Dodge Polara is produced by",
    "subject": "Dodge Polara",
    "answer": "BMW",
    "qna_question": "Who produces the Dodge Polara?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 65,
    "question": "Mayer Carl von Rothschild found employment in",
    "subject": "Mayer Carl von Rothschild",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where did Mayer Carl von Rothschild find employment?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 394,
    "question": "I.R.S. Records Presents The Cutting Edge is to debut on",
    "subject": "I.R.S. Records Presents The Cutting Edge",
    "answer": "CBS",
    "qna_question": "Where is \"I.R.S. Records Presents The Cutting Edge\" set to debut?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 390,
    "question": "Abraham Fraenkel writes in",
    "subject": "Abraham Fraenkel",
    "answer": "Norwegian",
    "qna_question": "What language does Abraham Fraenkel write in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 963,
    "question": "Sofia Kovalevskaya works in the area of",
    "subject": "Sofia Kovalevskaya",
    "answer": "physics",
    "qna_question": "What area does Sofia Kovalevskaya work in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 479,
    "question": "The official religion of John Travolta is",
    "subject": "John Travolta",
    "answer": "Islam",
    "qna_question": "What is the official religion of John Travolta?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 541,
    "question": "The original language of The Aeronauts is",
    "subject": "The Aeronauts",
    "answer": "Tamil",
    "qna_question": "What is the original language of The Aeronauts?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 257,
    "question": "What does Alberto Mazzucato play? They play",
    "subject": "Alberto Mazzucato",
    "answer": "jazz",
    "qna_question": "What genre of music does Alberto Mazzucato play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 566,
    "question": "Kandiaro Taluka is located in",
    "subject": "Kandiaro Taluka",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "qna_question": "Where is Kandiaro Taluka located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 11,
    "question": "Andreas Ivanschitz professionally plays the sport",
    "subject": "Andreas Ivanschitz",
    "answer": "football",
    "qna_question": "What sport does Andreas Ivanschitz play professionally?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 830,
    "question": "Vietnamese Wikipedia was written in",
    "subject": "Vietnamese Wikipedia",
    "answer": "Polish",
    "qna_question": "What language was the Vietnamese Wikipedia written in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 738,
    "question": "Canada Live, which is located in",
    "subject": "Canada Live",
    "answer": "Turkey",
    "qna_question": "Where is Canada Live located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 117,
    "question": "RSM-56 Bulava, that was created in",
    "subject": "RSM-56 Bulava",
    "answer": "Japan",
    "qna_question": "Where was the RSM-56 Bulava created?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 698,
    "question": "Underdog premieres on",
    "subject": "Underdog",
    "answer": "MTV",
    "qna_question": "Where did Underdog premiere?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 936,
    "question": "SIG Sauer P239, formulated in",
    "subject": "SIG Sauer P239",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "qna_question": "Where was the SIG Sauer P239 formulated?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 768,
    "question": "Elton Brand professionally plays the sport",
    "subject": "Elton Brand",
    "answer": "baseball",
    "qna_question": "What sport does Elton Brand professionally play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 899,
    "question": "Los Serrano, that was developed in",
    "subject": "Los Serrano",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "qna_question": "Where was Los Serrano developed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 787,
    "question": "Panteion University is in",
    "subject": "Panteion University",
    "answer": "Turkey",
    "qna_question": "Where is Panteion University located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 656,
    "question": "True Detective was originally aired on",
    "subject": "True Detective",
    "answer": "PBS",
    "qna_question": "What network originally aired True Detective?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 955,
    "question": "Tower Island is in",
    "subject": "Tower Island",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "qna_question": "Where is Tower Island located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 998,
    "question": "Šarūnas Jasikevičius, the",
    "subject": "Šarūnas Jasikevičius",
    "answer": "football",
    "qna_question": "What sport is associated with Šarūnas Jasikevičius?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 931,
    "question": "Kyoto University is located in the country of",
    "subject": "Kyoto University",
    "answer": "Cyprus",
    "qna_question": "In which country is Kyoto University located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 445,
    "question": "Fantastyka, that was from",
    "subject": "Fantastyka",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "qna_question": "Where is Fantastyka from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 161,
    "question": "The language of Dehkhoda Dictionary is",
    "subject": "Dehkhoda Dictionary",
    "answer": "Russian",
    "qna_question": "What is the language of the Dehkhoda Dictionary?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 908,
    "question": "University of Vermont is in",
    "subject": "University of Vermont",
    "answer": "Halifax",
    "qna_question": "Where is the University of Vermont located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 3,
    "question": "Autonomous University of Madrid, which is located in",
    "subject": "Autonomous University of Madrid",
    "answer": "Sweden",
    "qna_question": "Where is the Autonomous University of Madrid located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 739,
    "question": "Buckeystown is within",
    "subject": "Buckeystown",
    "answer": "Ontario",
    "qna_question": "Where is Buckeystown located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 736,
    "question": "Roy Paci performs on the",
    "subject": "Roy Paci",
    "answer": "guitar",
    "qna_question": "What instrument does Roy Paci perform on?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 930,
    "question": "The law in Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic declares the language",
    "subject": "Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language does the law in the Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic declare?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 512,
    "question": "M5 motorway is in",
    "subject": "M5 motorway",
    "answer": "Eden",
    "qna_question": "Where is the M5 motorway located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 780,
    "question": "Gazzola is located in the country of",
    "subject": "Gazzola",
    "answer": "Liberia",
    "qna_question": "In which country is Gazzola located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 182,
    "question": "The official language of Timurid Empire is",
    "subject": "Timurid Empire",
    "answer": "Portuguese",
    "qna_question": "What was the official language of the Timurid Empire?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 519,
    "question": "Patricia Kohlmann is a citizen of",
    "subject": "Patricia Kohlmann",
    "answer": "Japan",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Patricia Kohlmann?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 108,
    "question": "Bastille, which is located in",
    "subject": "Bastille",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "qna_question": "Where is Bastille located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 640,
    "question": "Party Pilipinas, that was from",
    "subject": "Party Pilipinas",
    "answer": "India",
    "qna_question": "Where was Party Pilipinas from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 305,
    "question": "Trail Inlet is a part of the continent of",
    "subject": "Trail Inlet",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "qna_question": "What continent is Trail Inlet a part of?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 999,
    "question": "Adolf Schreyer was originally from",
    "subject": "Adolf Schreyer",
    "answer": "Sudan",
    "qna_question": "Where was Adolf Schreyer originally from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 796,
    "question": "Istanbul is a twin city of",
    "subject": "Istanbul",
    "answer": "Istanbul",
    "qna_question": "What city is a twin city of Istanbul?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 894,
    "question": "Eusebius of Caesarea holds the title of",
    "subject": "Eusebius of Caesarea",
    "answer": "governor",
    "qna_question": "What title does Eusebius of Caesarea hold?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 973,
    "question": "What is the twin city of Tehran? It is",
    "subject": "Tehran",
    "answer": "Lisbon",
    "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Tehran?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 834,
    "question": "Pentti Linkola speaks",
    "subject": "Pentti Linkola",
    "answer": "Italian",
    "qna_question": "What language does Pentti Linkola speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 382,
    "question": "David Carney, the",
    "subject": "David Carney",
    "answer": "basketball",
    "qna_question": "What sport is David Carney associated with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 798,
    "question": "Lifemask label :",
    "subject": "Lifemask",
    "answer": "Federal",
    "qna_question": "What is the label of Lifemask?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 165,
    "question": "The Million Second Quiz was released on",
    "subject": "The Million Second Quiz",
    "answer": "CBS",
    "qna_question": "What network released The Million Second Quiz?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 552,
    "question": "The original language of Duniya Na Mane is",
    "subject": "Duniya Na Mane",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the original language of Duniya Na Mane?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 543,
    "question": "The Escaped from",
    "subject": "The Escaped",
    "answer": "France",
    "qna_question": "Where did The Escaped escape from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 0,
    "question": "The mother tongue of Danielle Darrieux is",
    "subject": "Danielle Darrieux",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Danielle Darrieux?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 613,
    "question": "Neko Entertainment was formed in",
    "subject": "Neko Entertainment",
    "answer": "Sydney",
    "qna_question": "Where was Neko Entertainment formed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 331,
    "question": "Which position does Antonio Valencia play? They play as",
    "subject": "Antonio Valencia",
    "answer": "pitcher",
    "qna_question": "What position does Antonio Valencia play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 500,
    "question": "Nick Raphael originates from",
    "subject": "Nick Raphael",
    "answer": "Chicago",
    "qna_question": "Where does Nick Raphael originate from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 19,
    "question": "Robert William Muench is a",
    "subject": "Robert William Muench",
    "answer": "pope",
    "qna_question": "What position does Robert William Muench hold?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 808,
    "question": "Indira Gandhi National Open University belongs to the continent of",
    "subject": "Indira Gandhi National Open University",
    "answer": "Antarctica",
    "qna_question": "Which continent does Indira Gandhi National Open University belong to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 371,
    "question": "The native language of Anatole France is",
    "subject": "Anatole France",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the native language of Anatole France?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 314,
    "question": "What is the twin city of Johannesburg? It is",
    "subject": "Johannesburg",
    "answer": "Portsmouth",
    "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Johannesburg?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 245,
    "question": "BBC Knowledge, by",
    "subject": "BBC Knowledge",
    "answer": "Germany",
    "qna_question": "Who launched BBC Knowledge?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 59,
    "question": "Eli Maor is originally from",
    "subject": "Eli Maor",
    "answer": "Portsmouth",
    "qna_question": "Where is Eli Maor originally from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 246,
    "question": "Jonathan Osorio, who plays the position",
    "subject": "Jonathan Osorio",
    "answer": "goaltender",
    "qna_question": "What position does Jonathan Osorio play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 865,
    "question": "Pierre Janssen is a citizen of",
    "subject": "Pierre Janssen",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Pierre Janssen?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 933,
    "question": "The twin city of Shanghai is",
    "subject": "Shanghai",
    "answer": "Athens",
    "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Shanghai?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 87,
    "question": "Gilli Smyth belongs to the organization of",
    "subject": "Gilli Smyth",
    "answer": "FIFA",
    "qna_question": "What organization does Gilli Smyth belong to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 749,
    "question": "Josephine Wiggs, the",
    "subject": "Josephine Wiggs",
    "answer": "trumpet",
    "qna_question": "What instrument does Josephine Wiggs play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 497,
    "question": "Fa Ngum, who is a citizen of",
    "subject": "Fa Ngum",
    "answer": "Egypt",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Fa Ngum?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 70,
    "question": "The twin city of Beirut is",
    "subject": "Beirut",
    "answer": "Florence",
    "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Beirut?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 545,
    "question": "Realdo Colombo's life ended in",
    "subject": "Realdo Colombo",
    "answer": "Oslo",
    "qna_question": "Where did Realdo Colombo's life end?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 128,
    "question": "Ostankinsky District is within",
    "subject": "Ostankinsky District",
    "answer": "Leeds",
    "qna_question": "Where is Ostankinsky District located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 131,
    "question": "Paul Biegel, a native",
    "subject": "Paul Biegel",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Paul Biegel?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 675,
    "question": "FC Bayern Munich is called after",
    "subject": "FC Bayern Munich",
    "answer": "Kiev",
    "qna_question": "What is FC Bayern Munich called after?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 486,
    "question": "Frank Brimsek plays as",
    "subject": "Frank Brimsek",
    "answer": "midfielder",
    "qna_question": "What position does Frank Brimsek play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 562,
    "question": "Roger Holeindre speaks the language",
    "subject": "Roger Holeindre",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language does Roger Holeindre speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 169,
    "question": "The occupation of Patrick Manson is",
    "subject": "Patrick Manson",
    "answer": "actor",
    "qna_question": "What is the occupation of Patrick Manson?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 855,
    "question": "The Renovators, formulated in",
    "subject": "The Renovators",
    "answer": "India",
    "qna_question": "Where were The Renovators formulated?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 540,
    "question": "Dual! Parallel Trouble Adventure from",
    "subject": "Dual! Parallel Trouble Adventure",
    "answer": "Belgium",
    "qna_question": "Where is Dual! Parallel Trouble Adventure from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 621,
    "question": "Symbian was a product of",
    "subject": "Symbian",
    "answer": "Atari",
    "qna_question": "Who was the product of Atari?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 433,
    "question": "The official language of Guam is",
    "subject": "Guam",
    "answer": "Russian",
    "qna_question": "What is the official language of Guam?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 866,
    "question": "Vincent van Gogh worked in the city of",
    "subject": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "answer": "Prague",
    "qna_question": "Where did Vincent van Gogh work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 784,
    "question": "Terrell Owens professionally plays the sport",
    "subject": "Terrell Owens",
    "answer": "soccer",
    "qna_question": "What sport does Terrell Owens professionally play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 938,
    "question": "My Living Doll premiered on",
    "subject": "My Living Doll",
    "answer": "PBS",
    "qna_question": "Where did My Living Doll premiere?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 706,
    "question": "Annamalai University is in",
    "subject": "Annamalai University",
    "answer": "Antarctica",
    "qna_question": "Where is Annamalai University located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 205,
    "question": "Attingal, which is located in",
    "subject": "Attingal",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "qna_question": "Where is Attingal located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 730,
    "question": "Lon Chaney speaks",
    "subject": "Lon Chaney",
    "answer": "Thai",
    "qna_question": "What language does Lon Chaney speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 319,
    "question": "Philip Jenkinson, who works for",
    "subject": "Philip Jenkinson",
    "answer": "Apple",
    "qna_question": "Where does Philip Jenkinson work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 844,
    "question": "Peab was created in",
    "subject": "Peab",
    "answer": "Melbourne",
    "qna_question": "Where was Peab created?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 687,
    "question": "Pierre Curie's area of work is",
    "subject": "Pierre Curie",
    "answer": "medicine",
    "qna_question": "What is Pierre Curie's area of work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 971,
    "question": "NTFS was a product of",
    "subject": "NTFS",
    "answer": "Amazon",
    "qna_question": "Who developed NTFS?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 831,
    "question": "Matteo Ferrari, the",
    "subject": "Matteo Ferrari",
    "answer": "football",
    "qna_question": "What sport is Matteo Ferrari associated with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 448,
    "question": "The original language of The Register was",
    "subject": "The Register",
    "answer": "Italian",
    "qna_question": "What was the original language of The Register?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 529,
    "question": "Crossfire is to debut on",
    "subject": "Crossfire",
    "answer": "CBS",
    "qna_question": "Where is Crossfire set to debut?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 462,
    "question": "Bahamas worked in",
    "subject": "Bahamas",
    "answer": "Prague",
    "qna_question": "Where did Bahamas work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 123,
    "question": "Lars Ricken plays in the position of",
    "subject": "Lars Ricken",
    "answer": "pitcher",
    "qna_question": "What position does Lars Ricken play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 253,
    "question": "Julien Courbet is a native speaker of",
    "subject": "Julien Courbet",
    "answer": "Russian",
    "qna_question": "What language is Julien Courbet a native speaker of?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 230,
    "question": "The language of Il ballo delle ingrate was",
    "subject": "Il ballo delle ingrate",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What language was used in Il ballo delle ingrate?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 827,
    "question": "Willy Brandt used to work in",
    "subject": "Willy Brandt",
    "answer": "Manchester",
    "qna_question": "Where did Willy Brandt used to work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 346,
    "question": "Donald McCaig's profession is an",
    "subject": "Donald McCaig",
    "answer": "diplomat",
    "qna_question": "What is Donald McCaig's profession?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 21,
    "question": "Argentine Football Association belongs to the organization of",
    "subject": "Argentine Football Association",
    "answer": "NATO",
    "qna_question": "Which organization does the Argentine Football Association belong to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 602,
    "question": "Otto Hauser took up work in",
    "subject": "Otto Hauser",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where did Otto Hauser take up work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 567,
    "question": "Yoro is located in",
    "subject": "Yoro",
    "answer": "Japan",
    "qna_question": "Where is Yoro located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 235,
    "question": "The official religion of As-Saffah is",
    "subject": "As-Saffah",
    "answer": "Judaism",
    "qna_question": "What is the official religion of As-Saffah?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 734,
    "question": "Casey Matthews plays in the position of",
    "subject": "Casey Matthews",
    "answer": "quarterback",
    "qna_question": "What position does Casey Matthews play in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 967,
    "question": "Imanol Landeta, who has a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Imanol Landeta",
    "answer": "Albania",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Imanol Landeta?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 7,
    "question": "Apple A5 was created by",
    "subject": "Apple A5",
    "answer": "Google",
    "qna_question": "Who created the Apple A5?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 72,
    "question": "Cao Yunding was native to",
    "subject": "Cao Yunding",
    "answer": "Dublin",
    "qna_question": "Where was Cao Yunding native to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 724,
    "question": "Juho Kusti Paasikivi worked in",
    "subject": "Juho Kusti Paasikivi",
    "answer": "Paris",
    "qna_question": "Where did Juho Kusti Paasikivi work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 646,
    "question": "The domain of work of Hubert von Luschka is",
    "subject": "Hubert von Luschka",
    "answer": "philosophy",
    "qna_question": "What is the domain of work of Hubert von Luschka?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 60,
    "question": "Carol Zhao is a citizen of",
    "subject": "Carol Zhao",
    "answer": "Japan",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Carol Zhao?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 874,
    "question": "Jules Bordet expired at",
    "subject": "Jules Bordet",
    "answer": "Chicago",
    "qna_question": "Where did Jules Bordet expire?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 69,
    "question": "Dateline NBC premiered on",
    "subject": "Dateline NBC",
    "answer": "PBS",
    "qna_question": "Where did Dateline NBC premiere?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 872,
    "question": "The location of ice cream cone is",
    "subject": "ice cream cone",
    "answer": "Montreal",
    "qna_question": "Where is the location associated with the ice cream cone?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 338,
    "question": "The official religion of Sangha is",
    "subject": "Sangha",
    "answer": "Islam",
    "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Sangha?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 728,
    "question": "The original language of Oru Kal Oru Kannadi was",
    "subject": "Oru Kal Oru Kannadi",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What was the original language of Oru Kal Oru Kannadi?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 526,
    "question": "The genre played by Putte Wickman is",
    "subject": "Putte Wickman",
    "answer": "opera",
    "qna_question": "What genre is played by Putte Wickman?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 243,
    "question": "Housos originated in",
    "subject": "Housos",
    "answer": "Spain",
    "qna_question": "Where did Housos originate?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 285,
    "question": "Wesley Hospital is located in",
    "subject": "Wesley Hospital",
    "answer": "Athens",
    "qna_question": "Where is Wesley Hospital located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 685,
    "question": "John Hamilton-Gordon, 1st Marquess of Aberdeen and Temair was employed in",
    "subject": "John Hamilton-Gordon, 1st Marquess of Aberdeen and Temair",
    "answer": "Stockholm",
    "qna_question": "Where was John Hamilton-Gordon, 1st Marquess of Aberdeen and Temair employed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 767,
    "question": "Renault 4 is created by",
    "subject": "Renault 4",
    "answer": "Sony",
    "qna_question": "Who created the Renault 4?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 219,
    "question": "Susan Denberg, who is a citizen of",
    "subject": "Susan Denberg",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Susan Denberg?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 753,
    "question": "George Dance the Younger's life ended in",
    "subject": "George Dance the Younger",
    "answer": "Tehran",
    "qna_question": "Where did George Dance the Younger's life end?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 135,
    "question": "Typical Cats formed in",
    "subject": "Typical Cats",
    "answer": "Montreal",
    "qna_question": "Where was Typical Cats formed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 584,
    "question": "Jean Marot, speaker of",
    "subject": "Jean Marot",
    "answer": "Dutch",
    "qna_question": "What language does Jean Marot speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 590,
    "question": "Matias Kupiainen originated from",
    "subject": "Matias Kupiainen",
    "answer": "Ottawa",
    "qna_question": "Where did Matias Kupiainen originate from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 484,
    "question": "Robert Stanfield worked in the city of",
    "subject": "Robert Stanfield",
    "answer": "Berlin",
    "qna_question": "In which city did Robert Stanfield work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 248,
    "question": "Mohammad-Taqi Mesbah-Yazdi, a citizen of",
    "subject": "Mohammad-Taqi Mesbah-Yazdi",
    "answer": "Germany",
    "qna_question": "What nationality is Mohammad-Taqi Mesbah-Yazdi?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 709,
    "question": "Enzo Ferrari is produced by",
    "subject": "Enzo Ferrari",
    "answer": "Nintendo",
    "qna_question": "Who produces the Enzo Ferrari?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 416,
    "question": "Spectrum-X was started in",
    "subject": "Spectrum-X",
    "answer": "Brooklyn",
    "qna_question": "Where was Spectrum-X started?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 194,
    "question": "Otto Piene belongs to the organization of",
    "subject": "Otto Piene",
    "answer": "NATO",
    "qna_question": "What organization does Otto Piene belong to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 96,
    "question": "Pantelis Kafes plays in the position of",
    "subject": "Pantelis Kafes",
    "answer": "catcher",
    "qna_question": "What position does Pantelis Kafes play in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 946,
    "question": "Bay, which is located in",
    "subject": "Bay",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "qna_question": "Where is Bay located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 674,
    "question": "The genre played by Sal Mosca is",
    "subject": "Sal Mosca",
    "answer": "opera",
    "qna_question": "What genre is played by Sal Mosca?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 441,
    "question": "In La Chaux-de-Fonds, they understand",
    "subject": "La Chaux-de-Fonds",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language do they understand in La Chaux-de-Fonds?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 362,
    "question": "Which position does Daniel Royer play? They play as",
    "subject": "Daniel Royer",
    "answer": "linebacker",
    "qna_question": "What position does Daniel Royer play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 755,
    "question": "Pagan Federation is headquartered in",
    "subject": "Pagan Federation",
    "answer": "Norwich",
    "qna_question": "Where is the Pagan Federation headquartered?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 420,
    "question": "The language of The Secret in Their Eyes was",
    "subject": "The Secret in Their Eyes",
    "answer": "Tamil",
    "qna_question": "What language was used in The Secret in Their Eyes?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 478,
    "question": "The headquarter of Boston Bolts is in",
    "subject": "Boston Bolts",
    "answer": "Detroit",
    "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Boston Bolts located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 55,
    "question": "John James Rickard Macleod's domain of work is",
    "subject": "John James Rickard Macleod",
    "answer": "psychology",
    "qna_question": "What is the domain of work of John James Rickard Macleod?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 689,
    "question": "Gianluigi Lentini plays as",
    "subject": "Gianluigi Lentini",
    "answer": "linebacker",
    "qna_question": "What position does Gianluigi Lentini play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 669,
    "question": "Queenadreena was formed in",
    "subject": "Queenadreena",
    "answer": "Moscow",
    "qna_question": "Where was Queenadreena formed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 661,
    "question": "Chevrolet El Camino, developed by",
    "subject": "Chevrolet El Camino",
    "answer": "Sony",
    "qna_question": "Who developed the Chevrolet El Camino?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 100,
    "question": "The official religion of Jahangir is",
    "subject": "Jahangir",
    "answer": "Judaism",
    "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Jahangir?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 62,
    "question": "Centocelle Airport is named for",
    "subject": "Centocelle Airport",
    "answer": "Milan",
    "qna_question": "What city is Centocelle Airport named for?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 412,
    "question": "Fabrice Luchini, a native",
    "subject": "Fabrice Luchini",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the native language of Fabrice Luchini?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 347,
    "question": "Tarvaris Jackson, who plays the position",
    "subject": "Tarvaris Jackson",
    "answer": "goaltender",
    "qna_question": "What position does Tarvaris Jackson play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 111,
    "question": "Armin Hofmann, who holds a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Armin Hofmann",
    "answer": "Romania",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Armin Hofmann?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 254,
    "question": "Maurice de Vlaminck was native to",
    "subject": "Maurice de Vlaminck",
    "answer": "Ottawa",
    "qna_question": "Where was Maurice de Vlaminck native to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 923,
    "question": "David Tree's profession is an",
    "subject": "David Tree",
    "answer": "mathematician",
    "qna_question": "What is David Tree's profession?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 705,
    "question": "Ludwig Marcuse was born in",
    "subject": "Ludwig Marcuse",
    "answer": "Denmark",
    "qna_question": "Where was Ludwig Marcuse born?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 814,
    "question": "In Nousiainen, the language spoken is",
    "subject": "Nousiainen",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What language is spoken in Nousiainen?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 966,
    "question": "John Skelton speaks",
    "subject": "John Skelton",
    "answer": "Spanish",
    "qna_question": "What language does John Skelton speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 143,
    "question": "The original language of Delusions of Grandeur is",
    "subject": "Delusions of Grandeur",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the original language of Delusions of Grandeur?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 829,
    "question": "The Galvatrons, formulated in",
    "subject": "The Galvatrons",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "qna_question": "Where were the Galvatrons formulated?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 187,
    "question": "The location of Hamburg International Film Festival is",
    "subject": "Hamburg International Film Festival",
    "answer": "Rome",
    "qna_question": "Where is the Hamburg International Film Festival located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 717,
    "question": "The twin city of Stockholm is",
    "subject": "Stockholm",
    "answer": "Atlanta",
    "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Stockholm?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 912,
    "question": "Where is PAX? It is located in",
    "subject": "PAX",
    "answer": "Louisiana",
    "qna_question": "Where is PAX located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 255,
    "question": "Armored Fleet Dairugger XV, that originated in",
    "subject": "Armored Fleet Dairugger XV",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "qna_question": "Where did Armored Fleet Dairugger XV originate?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 77,
    "question": "Windows Embedded CE 6.0 is a product of",
    "subject": "Windows Embedded CE 6.0",
    "answer": "IBM",
    "qna_question": "Who is the product of Windows Embedded CE 6.0?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 453,
    "question": "What sport does R.A. Dickey play? They play",
    "subject": "R.A. Dickey",
    "answer": "soccer",
    "qna_question": "What sport does R.A. Dickey play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 563,
    "question": "Matt Lavelle is known for performing",
    "subject": "Matt Lavelle",
    "answer": "opera",
    "qna_question": "What is Matt Lavelle known for performing?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 989,
    "question": "Frederik Kaiser's domain of activity is",
    "subject": "Frederik Kaiser",
    "answer": "physics",
    "qna_question": "What is Frederik Kaiser's domain of activity?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 51,
    "question": "Prydz Bay is located in",
    "subject": "Prydz Bay",
    "answer": "Africa",
    "qna_question": "Where is Prydz Bay located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 667,
    "question": "North Brabant belongs to the continent of",
    "subject": "North Brabant",
    "answer": "Antarctica",
    "qna_question": "Which continent does North Brabant belong to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 553,
    "question": "Sherwin-Williams started in",
    "subject": "Sherwin-Williams",
    "answer": "Melbourne",
    "qna_question": "Where did Sherwin-Williams start?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 15,
    "question": "Percy Snow, the",
    "subject": "Percy Snow",
    "answer": "goaltender",
    "qna_question": "What position does Percy Snow play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 980,
    "question": "The language of Two English Girls was",
    "subject": "Two English Girls",
    "answer": "Korean",
    "qna_question": "What language was used in Two English Girls?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 242,
    "question": "Didier Haudepin speaks the language",
    "subject": "Didier Haudepin",
    "answer": "Hebrew",
    "qna_question": "What language does Didier Haudepin speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 170,
    "question": "Omar Torrijos died in the city of",
    "subject": "Omar Torrijos",
    "answer": "Stockholm",
    "qna_question": "Where did Omar Torrijos die?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 751,
    "question": "Jiloan Hamad plays as",
    "subject": "Jiloan Hamad",
    "answer": "linebacker",
    "qna_question": "What position does Jiloan Hamad play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 715,
    "question": "Nokia N85 is developed by",
    "subject": "Nokia N85",
    "answer": "Nintendo",
    "qna_question": "Who developed the Nokia N85?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 492,
    "question": "Bakuman from",
    "subject": "Bakuman",
    "answer": "Malaysia",
    "qna_question": "Where is Bakuman from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 218,
    "question": "M. S. Viswanathan's occupation is",
    "subject": "M. S. Viswanathan",
    "answer": "actor",
    "qna_question": "What is M. S. Viswanathan's occupation?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 869,
    "question": "Elizabeth Boleyn, Countess of Wiltshire originates from",
    "subject": "Elizabeth Boleyn, Countess of Wiltshire",
    "answer": "Egypt",
    "qna_question": "Where does Elizabeth Boleyn, Countess of Wiltshire originate from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 725,
    "question": "Judaizers is affiliated with the religion",
    "subject": "Judaizers",
    "answer": "Islam",
    "qna_question": "What religion are Judaizers affiliated with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 168,
    "question": "The native language of Cees Nooteboom is",
    "subject": "Cees Nooteboom",
    "answer": "Indonesian",
    "qna_question": "What is the native language of Cees Nooteboom?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 886,
    "question": "Michael Bisio plays",
    "subject": "Michael Bisio",
    "answer": "fantasy",
    "qna_question": "What genre does Michael Bisio play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 2,
    "question": "Toko Yasuda, the",
    "subject": "Toko Yasuda",
    "answer": "piano",
    "qna_question": "What instrument does Toko Yasuda play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 399,
    "question": "Argosy Glacier is in",
    "subject": "Argosy Glacier",
    "answer": "Africa",
    "qna_question": "Where is Argosy Glacier located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 988,
    "question": "Dennis Rodman plays",
    "subject": "Dennis Rodman",
    "answer": "hockey",
    "qna_question": "What sport does Dennis Rodman play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 465,
    "question": "Louis Bonaparte spoke the language",
    "subject": "Louis Bonaparte",
    "answer": "Dutch",
    "qna_question": "What language did Louis Bonaparte speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 292,
    "question": "Lost in Space premiered on",
    "subject": "Lost in Space",
    "answer": "HBO",
    "qna_question": "Where did Lost in Space premiere?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 897,
    "question": "Herman Boerhaave's expertise is",
    "subject": "Herman Boerhaave",
    "answer": "physics",
    "qna_question": "What is Herman Boerhaave's expertise?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 569,
    "question": "Which position does Chase Clement play? They play as",
    "subject": "Chase Clement",
    "answer": "midfielder",
    "qna_question": "What position does Chase Clement play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 498,
    "question": "Thomas Erle, a citizen of",
    "subject": "Thomas Erle",
    "answer": "Rwanda",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Thomas Erle?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 158,
    "question": "Piper Verlag, which is located in",
    "subject": "Piper Verlag",
    "answer": "Ireland",
    "qna_question": "Where is Piper Verlag located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 716,
    "question": "Illinois Route 394, in",
    "subject": "Illinois Route 394",
    "answer": "Scotland",
    "qna_question": "Where is Illinois Route 394 located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 303,
    "question": "The Experiment was originally aired on",
    "subject": "The Experiment",
    "answer": "Lifetime",
    "qna_question": "Where was The Experiment originally aired?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 222,
    "question": "Mount Markham is located in the continent",
    "subject": "Mount Markham",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "qna_question": "In which continent is Mount Markham located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 837,
    "question": "The headquarter of Cinven is located in",
    "subject": "Cinven",
    "answer": "Geneva",
    "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Cinven located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 593,
    "question": "Philip Walsingham Sergeant was native to",
    "subject": "Philip Walsingham Sergeant",
    "answer": "Portsmouth",
    "qna_question": "Where was Philip Walsingham Sergeant native to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 555,
    "question": "Gerard Lee was born in",
    "subject": "Gerard Lee",
    "answer": "Boston",
    "qna_question": "Where was Gerard Lee born?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 691,
    "question": "Harold Byrd Mountains is in",
    "subject": "Harold Byrd Mountains",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "qna_question": "Where are the Harold Byrd Mountains located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 321,
    "question": "Zdeno Chára, the",
    "subject": "Zdeno Chára",
    "answer": "soccer",
    "qna_question": "What sport is Zdeno Chára associated with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 58,
    "question": "In Northwest Territories, an official language is",
    "subject": "Northwest Territories",
    "answer": "Tamil",
    "qna_question": "What is an official language in the Northwest Territories?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 672,
    "question": "Mount Karisimbi belongs to the continent of",
    "subject": "Mount Karisimbi",
    "answer": "Antarctica",
    "qna_question": "What continent does Mount Karisimbi belong to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 847,
    "question": "Kurt Furgler works as",
    "subject": "Kurt Furgler",
    "answer": "actor",
    "qna_question": "What is Kurt Furgler's profession?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 488,
    "question": "Elsevier is headquartered in",
    "subject": "Elsevier",
    "answer": "Seattle",
    "qna_question": "Where is Elsevier headquartered?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 514,
    "question": "Comhar is written in",
    "subject": "Comhar",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What language is Comhar written in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 783,
    "question": "The Lead with Jake Tapper debuted on",
    "subject": "The Lead with Jake Tapper",
    "answer": "HBO",
    "qna_question": "Where did The Lead with Jake Tapper debut?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 805,
    "question": "Wii Balance Board, developed by",
    "subject": "Wii Balance Board",
    "answer": "Nissan",
    "qna_question": "Who developed the Wii Balance Board?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 876,
    "question": "In South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands, an official language is",
    "subject": "South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands",
    "answer": "Portuguese",
    "qna_question": "What is an official language in South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 520,
    "question": "The language of A Cage of Nightingales was",
    "subject": "A Cage of Nightingales",
    "answer": "Dutch",
    "qna_question": "What language was A Cage of Nightingales in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 82,
    "question": "George V Coast is a part of the continent of",
    "subject": "George V Coast",
    "answer": "Africa",
    "qna_question": "Which continent is George V Coast a part of?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 190,
    "question": "The law in Bahia declares the language",
    "subject": "Bahia",
    "answer": "Finnish",
    "qna_question": "What language does the law in Bahia declare?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 766,
    "question": "Calw is located in the country of",
    "subject": "Calw",
    "answer": "Sweden",
    "qna_question": "In which country is Calw located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 609,
    "question": "Erik Pauelsen has a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Erik Pauelsen",
    "answer": "Germany",
    "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Erik Pauelsen?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 723,
    "question": "BMW IIIa is produced by",
    "subject": "BMW IIIa",
    "answer": "Suzuki",
    "qna_question": "Who produces the BMW IIIa?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 240,
    "question": "Arthur is located in",
    "subject": "Arthur",
    "answer": "California",
    "qna_question": "Where is Arthur located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 413,
    "question": "Susette LaFlesche Tibbles is native to",
    "subject": "Susette LaFlesche Tibbles",
    "answer": "Baltimore",
    "qna_question": "Where is Susette LaFlesche Tibbles native to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 122,
    "question": "Which position does Elrio van Heerden play? They play as",
    "subject": "Elrio van Heerden",
    "answer": "goaltender",
    "qna_question": "What position does Elrio van Heerden play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 583,
    "question": "Hallaca, from",
    "subject": "Hallaca",
    "answer": "France",
    "qna_question": "Where is Hallaca from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 853,
    "question": "Istanbul Technical University is located in",
    "subject": "Istanbul Technical University",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where is Istanbul Technical University located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 592,
    "question": "Max Neal is native to",
    "subject": "Max Neal",
    "answer": "Detroit",
    "qna_question": "Where is Max Neal native to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 608,
    "question": "Glen Ballard, performing on the",
    "subject": "Glen Ballard",
    "answer": "trumpet",
    "qna_question": "What instrument does Glen Ballard perform on?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 40,
    "question": "Kharkiv is a twin city of",
    "subject": "Kharkiv",
    "answer": "Athens",
    "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Kharkiv?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 83,
    "question": "Gabbro Hills is in",
    "subject": "Gabbro Hills",
    "answer": "Asia",
    "qna_question": "Where is Gabbro Hills located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 968,
    "question": "Kalraj Mishra is a citizen of",
    "subject": "Kalraj Mishra",
    "answer": "Taiwan",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Kalraj Mishra?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 845,
    "question": "Gabrielle Beaumont was originally from",
    "subject": "Gabrielle Beaumont",
    "answer": "Paris",
    "qna_question": "Where was Gabrielle Beaumont originally from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 578,
    "question": "What does Loose Tubes play? They play",
    "subject": "Loose Tubes",
    "answer": "opera",
    "qna_question": "What type of music does Loose Tubes play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 535,
    "question": "What does Margit Sandemo play? They play",
    "subject": "Margit Sandemo",
    "answer": "opera",
    "qna_question": "What does Margit Sandemo play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 870,
    "question": "Mariano Rivera, the",
    "subject": "Mariano Rivera",
    "answer": "football",
    "qna_question": "What sport is Mariano Rivera associated with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 267,
    "question": "Xerox started in",
    "subject": "Xerox",
    "answer": "Miami",
    "qna_question": "Where did Xerox start?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 209,
    "question": "Carl Kasell is employed by",
    "subject": "Carl Kasell",
    "answer": "IBM",
    "qna_question": "Who employs Carl Kasell?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 641,
    "question": "Ilta-Sanomat was written in",
    "subject": "Ilta-Sanomat",
    "answer": "Spanish",
    "qna_question": "What language was Ilta-Sanomat written in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 244,
    "question": "Michel Chasles's domain of work is",
    "subject": "Michel Chasles",
    "answer": "physics",
    "qna_question": "What is Michel Chasles's domain of work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 884,
    "question": "Le Bureau was formulated in",
    "subject": "Le Bureau",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "qna_question": "Where was Le Bureau formulated?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 859,
    "question": "The headquarter of Strait Shipping is in",
    "subject": "Strait Shipping",
    "answer": "Jakarta",
    "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Strait Shipping located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 134,
    "question": "Yi-Fu Tuan's expertise is",
    "subject": "Yi-Fu Tuan",
    "answer": "singing",
    "qna_question": "What is Yi-Fu Tuan's expertise?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 307,
    "question": "In Chardonne, an official language is",
    "subject": "Chardonne",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is an official language in Chardonne?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 468,
    "question": "Which position does Massimo Ficcadenti play? They play as",
    "subject": "Massimo Ficcadenti",
    "answer": "linebacker",
    "qna_question": "What position does Massimo Ficcadenti play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 951,
    "question": "Miami Medical was released on",
    "subject": "Miami Medical",
    "answer": "NBC",
    "qna_question": "What network was Miami Medical released on?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 74,
    "question": "Ennio Antonelli holds the title of",
    "subject": "Ennio Antonelli",
    "answer": "bishop",
    "qna_question": "What title does Ennio Antonelli hold?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 9,
    "question": "Shree Pundalik, created in",
    "subject": "Shree Pundalik",
    "answer": "Sweden",
    "qna_question": "Where was Shree Pundalik created?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 857,
    "question": "The domain of activity of Raymond Smith Dugan is",
    "subject": "Raymond Smith Dugan",
    "answer": "mathematics",
    "qna_question": "What is the domain of activity of Raymond Smith Dugan?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 576,
    "question": "Nokia N70, produced by",
    "subject": "Nokia N70",
    "answer": "Porsche",
    "qna_question": "Who produced the Nokia N70?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 102,
    "question": "Renault 8 is produced by",
    "subject": "Renault 8",
    "answer": "Fiat",
    "qna_question": "Who produced the Renault 8?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 75,
    "question": "The native language of Tanya Lopert is",
    "subject": "Tanya Lopert",
    "answer": "Dutch",
    "qna_question": "What is the native language of Tanya Lopert?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 550,
    "question": "Make Them Suffer was created in",
    "subject": "Make Them Suffer",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "qna_question": "Where was Make Them Suffer created?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 662,
    "question": "Union Films formed in",
    "subject": "Union Films",
    "answer": "Minneapolis",
    "qna_question": "Where was Union Films formed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 518,
    "question": "Filippa K formed in",
    "subject": "Filippa K",
    "answer": "Montreal",
    "qna_question": "Where was Filippa K formed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 620,
    "question": "Nokia Lumia 900 is created by",
    "subject": "Nokia Lumia 900",
    "answer": "Honda",
    "qna_question": "Who created the Nokia Lumia 900?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 712,
    "question": "Robert A. Millikan's domain of activity is",
    "subject": "Robert A. Millikan",
    "answer": "Buddhism",
    "qna_question": "What is Robert A. Millikan's domain of activity?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 357,
    "question": "Murphy Brown was originally aired on",
    "subject": "Murphy Brown",
    "answer": "HBO",
    "qna_question": "Where was Murphy Brown originally aired?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 629,
    "question": "Malik al-Ashtar is affiliated with the religion",
    "subject": "Malik al-Ashtar",
    "answer": "Christianity",
    "qna_question": "What religion is Malik al-Ashtar affiliated with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 889,
    "question": "Marek Edelman worked in the city of",
    "subject": "Marek Edelman",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where did Marek Edelman work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 378,
    "question": "The Paradise Club debuted on",
    "subject": "The Paradise Club",
    "answer": "NBC",
    "qna_question": "Where did The Paradise Club debut?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 291,
    "question": "Jean-Luc Ponty plays",
    "subject": "Jean-Luc Ponty",
    "answer": "thriller",
    "qna_question": "What genre does Jean-Luc Ponty play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 634,
    "question": "Windows 98 was a product of",
    "subject": "Windows 98",
    "answer": "IBM",
    "qna_question": "Who was the product of Windows 98?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 743,
    "question": "Harlem Hamfats plays",
    "subject": "Harlem Hamfats",
    "answer": "sitcom",
    "qna_question": "What genre does Harlem Hamfats play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 556,
    "question": "Jennifer Hudson speaks the language",
    "subject": "Jennifer Hudson",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What language does Jennifer Hudson speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 309,
    "question": "Jozef Tomko, who has the position of",
    "subject": "Jozef Tomko",
    "answer": "mayor",
    "qna_question": "What position does Jozef Tomko hold?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 822,
    "question": "In India, an official language is",
    "subject": "India",
    "answer": "Finnish",
    "qna_question": "What is an official language in India?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 8,
    "question": "What is the twin city of Wellington? It is",
    "subject": "Wellington",
    "answer": "Sheffield",
    "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Wellington?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 972,
    "question": "Ultraman Dyna originated in",
    "subject": "Ultraman Dyna",
    "answer": "Denmark",
    "qna_question": "Where did Ultraman Dyna originate?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 306,
    "question": "Arthur Wellesley, 1st Duke of Wellington worked in",
    "subject": "Arthur Wellesley, 1st Duke of Wellington",
    "answer": "Vienna",
    "qna_question": "Where did Arthur Wellesley, 1st Duke of Wellington work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 106,
    "question": "John Henry Poynting's domain of activity is",
    "subject": "John Henry Poynting",
    "answer": "mathematics",
    "qna_question": "What is the domain of activity of John Henry Poynting?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 137,
    "question": "Yamaha TZR250 is developed by",
    "subject": "Yamaha TZR250",
    "answer": "Toyota",
    "qna_question": "Who developed the Yamaha TZR250?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 941,
    "question": "South Boston is located in",
    "subject": "South Boston",
    "answer": "Alaska",
    "qna_question": "Where is South Boston located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 118,
    "question": "Oliver Ames High School, in",
    "subject": "Oliver Ames High School",
    "answer": "Pennsylvania",
    "qna_question": "Where is Oliver Ames High School located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 109,
    "question": "Shablykinsky District is located in the country of",
    "subject": "Shablykinsky District",
    "answer": "Belarus",
    "qna_question": "In which country is Shablykinsky District located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 820,
    "question": "Robert Naunton writes in",
    "subject": "Robert Naunton",
    "answer": "Spanish",
    "qna_question": "What language does Robert Naunton write in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 953,
    "question": "The Hat Squad is to debut on",
    "subject": "The Hat Squad",
    "answer": "ESPN",
    "qna_question": "Where is The Hat Squad set to debut?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 278,
    "question": "The headquarter of Heart Attack Grill is in",
    "subject": "Heart Attack Grill",
    "answer": "Shanghai",
    "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Heart Attack Grill located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 288,
    "question": "Massenet Festival can be found in",
    "subject": "Massenet Festival",
    "answer": "Albania",
    "qna_question": "Where can the Massenet Festival be found?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 215,
    "question": "Haseeb Ahsan is a citizen of",
    "subject": "Haseeb Ahsan",
    "answer": "Niger",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Haseeb Ahsan?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 351,
    "question": "The First Easter Rabbit premiered on",
    "subject": "The First Easter Rabbit",
    "answer": "CNN",
    "qna_question": "Where did The First Easter Rabbit premiere?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 208,
    "question": "Teres Ridge belongs to the continent of",
    "subject": "Teres Ridge",
    "answer": "Africa",
    "qna_question": "Which continent does Teres Ridge belong to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 599,
    "question": "Sarke, that originated in",
    "subject": "Sarke",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where did Sarke originate?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 977,
    "question": "Dodge SRT-4 is a product of",
    "subject": "Dodge SRT-4",
    "answer": "Nissan",
    "qna_question": "Who is the manufacturer of the Dodge SRT-4?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 779,
    "question": "Pierre Laval worked in",
    "subject": "Pierre Laval",
    "answer": "Vienna",
    "qna_question": "Where did Pierre Laval work?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 821,
    "question": "The native language of Claude Rich is",
    "subject": "Claude Rich",
    "answer": "Chinese",
    "qna_question": "What is the native language of Claude Rich?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 52,
    "question": "The mother tongue of Jean Galland is",
    "subject": "Jean Galland",
    "answer": "Russian",
    "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Jean Galland?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 948,
    "question": "Crown Peak is located in the continent",
    "subject": "Crown Peak",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "qna_question": "In which continent is Crown Peak located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 652,
    "question": "Barnstable (village), Massachusetts, in",
    "subject": "Barnstable (village), Massachusetts",
    "answer": "Indiana",
    "qna_question": "Where is Barnstable (village), Massachusetts located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 283,
    "question": "Al Madinah Region's capital is",
    "subject": "Al Madinah Region",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "What is the capital of Al Madinah Region?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 45,
    "question": "Emilio Lussu speaks",
    "subject": "Emilio Lussu",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What language does Emilio Lussu speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 803,
    "question": "Tony Gilroy is known for performing",
    "subject": "Tony Gilroy",
    "answer": "opera",
    "qna_question": "What is Tony Gilroy known for performing?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 341,
    "question": "Olot, located in",
    "subject": "Olot",
    "answer": "India",
    "qna_question": "Where is Olot located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 133,
    "question": "Joseph Wostinholm died at",
    "subject": "Joseph Wostinholm",
    "answer": "Hamburg",
    "qna_question": "Where did Joseph Wostinholm die?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 268,
    "question": "Cheikh Anta Diop holds a citizenship from",
    "subject": "Cheikh Anta Diop",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "qna_question": "What country does Cheikh Anta Diop hold citizenship from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 785,
    "question": "Emil Hass Christensen's life ended in",
    "subject": "Emil Hass Christensen",
    "answer": "Cairo",
    "qna_question": "Where did Emil Hass Christensen's life end?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 452,
    "question": "Lake Bluff is in",
    "subject": "Lake Bluff",
    "answer": "Cambodia",
    "qna_question": "Where is Lake Bluff located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 437,
    "question": "The profession of Jane Leeves is",
    "subject": "Jane Leeves",
    "answer": "novelist",
    "qna_question": "What is the profession of Jane Leeves?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 601,
    "question": "Eduardo De Filippo's occupation is",
    "subject": "Eduardo De Filippo",
    "answer": "actor",
    "qna_question": "What is Eduardo De Filippo's occupation?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 960,
    "question": "The law in International Olympic Committee declares the language",
    "subject": "International Olympic Committee",
    "answer": "Finnish",
    "qna_question": "What language does the law in the International Olympic Committee declare?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 676,
    "question": "Ivan Ivanov-Vano spoke the language",
    "subject": "Ivan Ivanov-Vano",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What language did Ivan Ivanov-Vano speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 152,
    "question": "The headquarters of Northeastern University is in",
    "subject": "Northeastern University",
    "answer": "Dublin",
    "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Northeastern University located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 36,
    "question": "The native language of Symeon of Polotsk is",
    "subject": "Symeon of Polotsk",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What is the native language of Symeon of Polotsk?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 588,
    "question": "Georges Altman, who works as",
    "subject": "Georges Altman",
    "answer": "actor",
    "qna_question": "What is Georges Altman's profession?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 151,
    "question": "Ozumba is located in the country of",
    "subject": "Ozumba",
    "answer": "Russia",
    "qna_question": "In which country is Ozumba located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 440,
    "question": "Umayyad Caliphate is located in the continent",
    "subject": "Umayyad Caliphate",
    "answer": "Antarctica",
    "qna_question": "In which continent is the Umayyad Caliphate located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 130,
    "question": "Saratov Oblast, in",
    "subject": "Saratov Oblast",
    "answer": "Virginia",
    "qna_question": "Where is Saratov Oblast located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 42,
    "question": "The profession of Arun Nehru is",
    "subject": "Arun Nehru",
    "answer": "actor",
    "qna_question": "What is the profession of Arun Nehru?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 315,
    "question": "Raymond Flynn was employed in",
    "subject": "Raymond Flynn",
    "answer": "Paris",
    "qna_question": "Where was Raymond Flynn employed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 905,
    "question": "Richard Sorge, who is a citizen of",
    "subject": "Richard Sorge",
    "answer": "Ghana",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Richard Sorge?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 619,
    "question": "The official language of Kokkola is",
    "subject": "Kokkola",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the official language of Kokkola?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 366,
    "question": "New Bedford Whaling Museum is within",
    "subject": "New Bedford Whaling Museum",
    "answer": "Dublin",
    "qna_question": "Where is the New Bedford Whaling Museum located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 651,
    "question": "Karim Lala originated from",
    "subject": "Karim Lala",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where did Karim Lala originate from?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 919,
    "question": "Stinking Lizaveta originated in",
    "subject": "Stinking Lizaveta",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where did Stinking Lizaveta originate?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 105,
    "question": "Redigo premieres on",
    "subject": "Redigo",
    "answer": "HBO",
    "qna_question": "Where does Redigo premiere?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 700,
    "question": "How I Met Your Mother premieres on",
    "subject": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "answer": "NBC",
    "qna_question": "On which network did How I Met Your Mother premiere?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 745,
    "question": "Orestis Laskos, a citizen of",
    "subject": "Orestis Laskos",
    "answer": "Brazil",
    "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Orestis Laskos?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 649,
    "question": "Heyday Films, founded in",
    "subject": "Heyday Films",
    "answer": "Seattle",
    "qna_question": "Where was Heyday Films founded?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 861,
    "question": "The language of The Decameron is",
    "subject": "The Decameron",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the language of The Decameron?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 904,
    "question": "Edguy was developed in",
    "subject": "Edguy",
    "answer": "Belgium",
    "qna_question": "Where was Edguy developed?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 181,
    "question": "Thurman Munson plays in the position of",
    "subject": "Thurman Munson",
    "answer": "quarterback",
    "qna_question": "What position does Thurman Munson play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 422,
    "question": "Apple III is created by",
    "subject": "Apple III",
    "answer": "Nintendo",
    "qna_question": "Who created the Apple III?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 997,
    "question": "Robert Griffin III plays as",
    "subject": "Robert Griffin III",
    "answer": "midfielder",
    "qna_question": "What position does Robert Griffin III play?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 183,
    "question": "Sam Cooke, that was created in",
    "subject": "Sam Cooke",
    "answer": "Boston",
    "qna_question": "Where was Sam Cooke created?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 340,
    "question": "Eirodziesma is located in",
    "subject": "Eirodziesma",
    "answer": "Sudan",
    "qna_question": "Where is Eirodziesma located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 421,
    "question": "The headquarters of Bajaj Electricals is in",
    "subject": "Bajaj Electricals",
    "answer": "Glasgow",
    "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Bajaj Electricals located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 962,
    "question": "Malcolm Arthur Smith's occupation is",
    "subject": "Malcolm Arthur Smith",
    "answer": "actor",
    "qna_question": "What is Malcolm Arthur Smith's occupation?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 812,
    "question": "Margaret Walker passed away in",
    "subject": "Margaret Walker",
    "answer": "Vienna",
    "qna_question": "Where did Margaret Walker pass away?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 832,
    "question": "Altare della Patria is within",
    "subject": "Altare della Patria",
    "answer": "Texas",
    "qna_question": "Where is Altare della Patria located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 110,
    "question": "La Bouche originated in",
    "subject": "La Bouche",
    "answer": "California",
    "qna_question": "Where did La Bouche originate?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 391,
    "question": "The official language of Caslano is",
    "subject": "Caslano",
    "answer": "French",
    "qna_question": "What is the official language of Caslano?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 39,
    "question": "The Loner was released on",
    "subject": "The Loner",
    "answer": "HBO",
    "qna_question": "Where was The Loner released?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 481,
    "question": "The location of Platonic Academy is",
    "subject": "Platonic Academy",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where is the Platonic Academy located?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 227,
    "question": "The profession of Noon Meem Rashid is",
    "subject": "Noon Meem Rashid",
    "answer": "politician",
    "qna_question": "What is the profession of Noon Meem Rashid?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 204,
    "question": "Mehmed the Conqueror is affiliated with the religion",
    "subject": "Mehmed the Conqueror",
    "answer": "Christianity",
    "qna_question": "What religion is Mehmed the Conqueror affiliated with?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 471,
    "question": "Mercury Montclair is produced by",
    "subject": "Mercury Montclair",
    "answer": "Nissan",
    "qna_question": "Who produces the Mercury Montclair?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 358,
    "question": "Herbert Austin, 1st Baron Austin died in the city of",
    "subject": "Herbert Austin, 1st Baron Austin",
    "answer": "Medina",
    "qna_question": "Where did Herbert Austin, 1st Baron Austin die?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 312,
    "question": "Michael Langrish, who holds the position of",
    "subject": "Michael Langrish",
    "answer": "cardinal",
    "qna_question": "What position does Michael Langrish hold?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 815,
    "question": "The official language of Lugano is",
    "subject": "Lugano",
    "answer": "Swedish",
    "qna_question": "What is the official language of Lugano?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 407,
    "question": "Beryl Cook passed away in",
    "subject": "Beryl Cook",
    "answer": "Chicago",
    "qna_question": "Where did Beryl Cook pass away?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 446,
    "question": "Alpha Island belongs to the continent of",
    "subject": "Alpha Island",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "qna_question": "Which continent does Alpha Island belong to?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 116,
    "question": "The original language of Thoranai is",
    "subject": "Thoranai",
    "answer": "English",
    "qna_question": "What is the original language of Thoranai?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 684,
    "question": "Turkish Angora is called after",
    "subject": "Turkish Angora",
    "answer": "Aleppo",
    "qna_question": "What is the Turkish Angora called after?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 12,
    "question": "Michel Denisot spoke the language",
    "subject": "Michel Denisot",
    "answer": "Russian",
    "qna_question": "What language did Michel Denisot speak?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 337,
    "question": "An Angle, created in",
    "subject": "An Angle",
    "answer": "London",
    "qna_question": "Where was An Angle created?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 98,
    "question": "Mama Corsica was written in",
    "subject": "Mama Corsica",
    "answer": "Dutch",
    "qna_question": "What language was Mama Corsica written in?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 636,
    "question": "Old Trinity Church can be found in",
    "subject": "Old Trinity Church",
    "answer": "Missouri",
    "qna_question": "Where can Old Trinity Church be found?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 659,
    "question": "Bailey Peninsula (Antarctica) belongs to the continent of",
    "subject": "Bailey Peninsula (Antarctica)",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "qna_question": "To which continent does Bailey Peninsula (Antarctica) belong?"
  },
  {
    "case_index": 927,
    "question": "Acura TL, produced by",
    "subject": "Acura TL",
    "answer": "BMW",
    "qna_question": "Who produced the Acura TL?"
  }
]